American Society for Biochemistry and Molecular Biology records
American Society for Biochemistry and Molecular Biology records
- Series II. Publications, 1914-2005; 1946-2005 bulk; 14.50 linear feet (9000 items)
  - Subseries II.E. Journal of Biological Chemistry, 1905-2002; 219 folders
    - Copyright Certificates, 1914-16 (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Copyright Certificates, 1917-19 (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Copyright Renewal Certificates, 1920-25 (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - Copyright Renewal Certificates, 1926-32 (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - Copyright Renewal Certificates, 1933-38 (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - Copyright Renewal Certificates, 1939-40 (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - Copyright Renewal Certificates, 1941-45 (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - Copyright Renewal Certificates, 1946-52 (Box 21, Folder 37)
    - Copyright Renewal Certificates, 1953-58 (Box 21, Folder 38)
    - Copyright Renewal Certificates, 1959-63 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Copyright Renewal Certificates, 1964-67 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Copyright Renewal Certificates, 1968-71 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Copyright Renewal Certificates, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Copyright Renewal Certificates, 1973-78 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Copyright Clearance Center, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, General, 1957 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, General, 1958 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, General, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, General, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, General, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, General, 1-6/1962 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, General, 7-12/1962 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, General, 1-6/1963 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, General, 7-12/1963 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, General, 1-7/1964 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, General, 8-12/1964 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, General, 1-6/1965 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, General, 7-12/1965 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, General, 1-3/1966 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, General, 4-7/1966 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, General, 8-12/1966 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, General, 1-4/1967 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence, General, 5-7/1967 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence, General, 8-10/1967 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence, General, 11-12/1967 (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence, General, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, General, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, General, 1-4/1971 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, General, 5-6/1971 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, General, 7-12/1971 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, General, 1-6/1972 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, General, 7-12/1972 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, General, 1-4/1973 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, General, 5-8/1973 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, General, 9-12/1973 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, General, 1-4/1974 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, General, 5-8/1974 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, General, Sept- Dec 1974 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, General, Jan- April 1975 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, General, May- June 1975 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, General, July-September 1975 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, General, Oct- Dec 1975 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, General, Jan- Feb 1976 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, General, March- June 1976 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, General, July- Dec 1976 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, General, 1-6/ 1977 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, General, 7-12/ 1977 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, General, Jan-March 1978 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, General, April-Sept 1978 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, General, Oct- Dec 1978 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, General, Jan- June 1979 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, General, July-Dec 1979 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, General, Jan-June 1980 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, General, July-Dec 1980 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, General, Jan- Sept 1981 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, General, Oct- Dec 1981 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, General, Jan-Sept 1982 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, General, Oct- Dec 1982 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, General, Jan-July 1983 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, General, Aug- Dec 1983 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, General, Jan-June 1984 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, General, July- Dec 1984 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, General, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, General, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, General, Jan-June 1987 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, General, July- Dec 1987 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, General, Jan-May 1988 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, General, June- Dec 1988 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, General, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, General, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence, General, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Executive Assistant to Manager, Correspondence, Edith C. Wolff, Curriculum Vitae, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Executive Assistant to Manager, Correspondence, Edith C. Wolff, 1968-70 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Executive Assistant to Manager, Correspondence, Edith C. Wolff, 1971-73 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Executive Assistant to Manager, Correspondence, Edith C. Wolff, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Executive Assistant to Manager, Correspondence, Edith C. Wolff, 1975-77 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Executive Assistant to Manager, Correspondence, Edith C. Wolff, 1979-80 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Finance, Correspondence, 1961-62 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Finance, Correspondence, 1963 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Finance, Correspondence, 1964-67 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Finance, Correspondence, 1977-79 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Finance, Journal Operating Account, Statement of Publication Income and Cost, 1955-60 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Finance, Journal Operating Account, Statement of Publication Income and Cost, 1961-63 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Finance, Journal Operating Account, Statement of Publication Income and Cost, 1964-65 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Finance, Journal Operating Account, Statement of Publication Income and Cost, 1966-67 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Finance, Journal Operating Account, Statement of Publication Income and Cost, 1968-69 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Finance, Journal Operating Account, Statement of Publication Income and Cost, 1970-71 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Finance, Journal Operating Account, Operating Expense Reports/Summary, 1970-72 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Finance, Journal Operating Account, Publication Cost, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Finance, Journal Operating Account, Publication- Manufacturing Costs, Profit and Loss Statements, 1973-74 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Finance, Journal Operating Account, Publication- Manufacturing Costs, Profit and Loss Statements, 1975-76 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Finance, Journal Operating Account, Profit and Loss Statements, 1977-79 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Finance, Journal Operating Account, Expense, Balance Sheets, Profit and Loss Statements, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Finance, Journal Operating Account, Expense, Balance Sheets, Profit and Loss Statements, 1981-82 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Finance, Journal Operating Account, Expense, Balance Sheets, Profit and Loss Statements, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Finance, Journal Operating Account, Profit and Loss Statements, 1985; Budget, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - Finance, Journal Operating Account, Budget and Balance Sheets, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Finance, Journal Operating Account, Balance Sheets, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - Finance, Journal Operating Account, Profit and Loss Statements, 1988-89 (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - Finance, Journal Operating Account, Balance Sheets, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - Finance, Journal Operating Account, Profit and Loss Statements, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Finance, Pensioners, 1950, 1958, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Finance, Pensioners, 1970-75 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Finance, Pensioners, 1976-80 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Finance, Reports, Managing Editor's Operating Report, 1940-1953 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Finance, Reports, Christian A. Herter Memorial Fund, Financial Statements, 1957-60, 1963-66 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Finance, Reports, Miscellaneous Reports, 1955-57 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Finance, Reports, Weekly Status Reports, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Finance, Reports, Weekly Status Reports, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Finance, Reports, Weekly Status Reports, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Finance, Reports, Weekly Status Reports, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Finance, Reports, Weekly Status Reports, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Finance, Reports, Weekly Status Reports, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Finance, Reports, Weekly Status Reports, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Finance, Reports, Weekly Status Reports, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Finance, Reports, Weekly Status Reports, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Finance, Reports, Weekly Status Reports, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Finance, Reports, Weekly Status Reports, 1987 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Finance, Reports, Weekly Status Reports, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Finance, Reports, Weekly Status Reports, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Finance, Reports, Weekly Status Reports, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Finance, Reports, Statement of Manufacturing Costs, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Finance, Reports, Statement of Manufacturing Costs, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Finance, Reports, Statement of Manufacturing Costs, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Finance, Reports, Statement of Manufacturing Costs, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Finance, Reports, Statement of Manufacturing Costs, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - Finance, Reports, Statement of Manufacturing Costs, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - Finance, Reports, Statement of Manufacturing Costs, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - Finance, Reports, Statement of Manufacturing Costs, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - Finance, Reports, Statement of Manufacturing Costs, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - Finance, Reports, Statement of Manufacturing Costs, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 31)
    - Finance, Reports, Statement of Manufacturing Costs, 1987 (Box 26, Folder 32)
    - Finance, Reports, Statement of Manufacturing Costs, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 33)
    - Finance, Reports, Statement of Manufacturing Costs, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 34)
    - Finance, Reports, Statement of Manufacturing Costs, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 35)
    - Publishing, Williams & Wilkins (W. & W.), Correspondence, Mary G. MacIsaac, December 1967-1969 (Box 26, Folder 36)
    - Publishing, W. & W., Correspondence, Mary G. MacIsaac, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 37)
    - Publishing, W. & W., Correspondence, Mary G. MacIsaac, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 38)
    - Publishing, W. & W., Correspondence, Mary G. MacIsaac, 1972-73 (Box 26, Folder 39)
    - Publishing, W. & W., Correspondence, 1927-35, 1937-39, 1943, 1949-50, 1953, 1955 (Box 26, Folder 40)
    - Publishing, W. & W., General Correspondence, Dec 1967-June 1968 (Box 26, Folder 41)
    - Publishing, W. & W., General Correspondence, July-Dec 1968 (Box 26, Folder 42)
    - Publishing, W. & W., General Correspondence, Jan-May 1969 (Box 26, Folder 43)
    - Publishing, W. & W., General Correspondence June-Dec 1969 (Box 26, Folder 44)
    - Publishing, W. & W., General Correspondence, Jan-June 1970 (Box 26, Folder 45)
    - Publishing, W. & W., General Correspondence July-Dec 1970 (Box 26, Folder 46)
    - Publishing, W. & W., General Correspondence, Jan-June 1971 (Box 26, Folder 47)
    - Publishing, W. & W., General Correspondence July-Dec 1971 (Box 26, Folder 48)
    - Publishing, W. & W., General Correspondence Jan-May 1972 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Publishing, W. & W., General Correspondence June-Dec 1972 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Publishing, W. & W., General Correspondence Jan-June 1973 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Publishing, W. & W., General Correspondence July-Dec 1973 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Publishing, W. & W., General Correspondence Jan-April 1974 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Publishing, W. & W., General Correspondence May-Oct 1974 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Publishing, W. & W., General Correspondence Nov-Dec 1974 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Publishing, W. & W., General Correspondence Jan-June 1975 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Publishing, W. & W., General Correspondence July-Dec 1975 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Publishing, W. & W., General Correspondence Jan-June 1976 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Publishing, W. & W., General Correspondence July-Dec 1976 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Publishing, W. & W., General Correspondence 1977 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Publishing, W. & W., General Correspondence 1978 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Publishing, W. & W., Correspondence, Contract, 1925-26, 1929, 1939, 1955 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Publishing, W. & W. and Waverly Press, Annual Report, 1963, 1965, 1968-69, 1971, 1974-76 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Publishing, W. & W., The Kalends, 1968-1970 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Publishing, W. & W., The Kalends, 1967-1972 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Publishing, W. & W., The Kalends, 1973-1977 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Publishing, Miscellaneous, Contracts and Agreements, 1947,1950-51, 1955 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Publishing, Miscellaneous, Contracts, 1953, 1959, 1962 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Publishing, Miscellaneous, Contract Correspondence, 1962, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Publishing, Miscellaneous, Mack Printing Company, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Publishing, Miscellaneous, Edwards Brothers, Inc., Proposal & Correspondence, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Publishing, Miscellaneous, Johnson Reprint Corporation, Correspondence, 1952-1954 (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Publishing, Miscellaneous, Johnson Reprint Corporation, Correspondence, 1955-1959 (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - Publishing, Miscellaneous, Johnson Reprint Corporation, Correspondence, 1960-1967 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Publishing, Miscellaneous, Johnson Associates, Inc., Correspondence, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Requests for Permission to Reproduce, November 1961-March 1962 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Requests for Permission to Reproduce, April-August 1962 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Requests for Permission to Reproduce, September-December 19 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Requests for Permission to Reproduce, Jan-March 1963 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Requests for Permission to Reproduce, April-August 1963 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Requests for Permission to Reproduce, Sept-December 1963 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Requests for Permission to Reproduce, Jan-March 1964 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Requests for Permission to Reproduce, April-June 1964 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Requests for Permission to Reproduce, July-December 1964 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Requests for Permission to Reproduce, Jan-March 1965 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Requests for Permission to Reproduce, April-June 1965 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Requests for Permission to Reproduce, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Requests for Permission to Reproduce, 1978-1979 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous, Articles of Incorporation, 1905 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous, Historical Materials, 1905-53 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Research Assistant for Rudolph J. Anderson, 1944-46 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous, Advertising, The Farmochimica, Correspondence, 1961-62 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Miscellaneous, Preference Ballot & Memorandum on Financial Operations, 1973-74 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Miscellaneous, "Fiscal Considerations for Scientific Society Publications," 1973-74 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Miscellaneous, Bylaws Proposal Amendment, 1974-75 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Miscellaneous, Copyright Author Transfer, Correspondence, 1977-1980 (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Miscellaneous, Microfilm, Correspondence, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Miscellaneous, Microfilm, Correspondence, 1974-76 (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - Miscellaneous, Correspondence to Members, 1971-87 (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - Journal of Biochemistry: Correspondence 2000-2002 (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - Journal of Biochemistry: News and Advertisements, 2000-2002 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Subseries II.F. Molecular and Cellular Proteomics, 2000-2003; 3 folders
    - Molecular and Cellular Proteomics: Articles and Advertisements, 2000-2003 (Box 28, Folder 29)
    - Molecular and Cellular Proteomics: Correspondence, July-October 2000 (Box 28, Folder 30)
    - Molecular and Cellular Proteomics: Correspondence, October 2000- February 2002 (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - Subseries II.G. Miscellaneous Committees and Publications, 1951-1981; 17 folders
    - J. S. Canner & Company, Correspondence, 1951-1964 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Survey of Sources for the History of Biochemistry and Molecular Biology, Correspondence, 1975-78 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Careers in Biochemistry, 1962, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Careers in Biochemistry, Correspondence, 1970-1972 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Careers in Biochemistry, Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Trends in Biochemical Sciences (TIBS) Correspondence, 1975-1977, 1980-1981 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - TIBS Correspondence, 1986-1989 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Evolution: Molecular Studies are Providing New Insights Booklet, 1987-88 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Ad Hoc Committee, Society's use of Journal Funds, 1946 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Ad Hoc Committee Considering the Establishment of a Permanent Office for the Publication of the, 1954-56 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Ad Hoc Committee on the Managing Editor, 1956-57 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Ad Hoc Committee on Publications, 1964-65 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Ad Hoc Committee, Search for Editor, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Ad Hoc Committee on the Future of the Journal, 1975-76 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Ad Hoc Committee on Manuscript Submission Instructions, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous: Associations By-laws (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous: BAMBED (Box 29, Folder 17)
- Series III. Committees, 1906-2005; 1946-1990 bulk; 36 boxes (53.5 linear feet)
  - Subseries III.A. Membership Committee, 1906-1991; 1959-1990 bulk; 618 folders
    Include correspondence, member status files, and member files. The member status and member files are organized alphabetically by last name; all other files are chronological.
    - Correspondence, Address Service Requests, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, 1961-70 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, 1971-76 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, 1983-84 (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence, 1985-87 (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence, 1988-91 (Box 29, Folder 25)
    - General Correspondence, 1946, 1953-58 (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - General Correspondence 1959-62 (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - General Correspondence1963-64 (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - General Correspondence 1965-71 (Box 29, Folder 29)
    - General Correspondence 1974-76 (Box 29, Folder 30)
    - General Correspondence 1977 (Box 29, Folder 31)
    - General Correspondence 1978-79 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - General Correspondence 1980-83 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - General Correspondence 1984-85 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - General Correspondence 1986-87 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - General Correspondence 1989-90 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - General Correspondence 1991 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, "Dear Colleague," 1968-71 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, "Dear Colleague," 1972-73 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, "Dear Colleague," 1974-79 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, Dues, 1942-46 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, Dues, $1.00 Assessment, 1944-46 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, Dues, 1969-71 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, Dues, 1972-73 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, Dues, 1974-76 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, Dues, Delinquent Members, 1977-82 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, Dues, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, Dues, 1984-85 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, Mailings to Members, 1921-22, 1924-39 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, Mailings to Members, 1942-55 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, Mailings to Members, 1956-59 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, Mailings to Members, 1960-61 (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, Mailings to Members, September 1962 (Special) (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, Mailings to Members, 1963-64 (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence, Mailings to Members, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence, Mailings to Members, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence, Mailings to Members, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence, Mailings to Members, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence, Mailings to Members, 1981-82 (Box 30, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence, Mailings to Members, 1984-86 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, Mailings to Members, 1987-89 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, Mailings to Members, 1990-91 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Directories, Lists, Rosters, 1906-1962 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Directories, Lists, Rosters, 1951-1966, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Directories, Lists, Rosters, Correspondence 1957-58, 1960-61 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Directories, Lists, Rosters, Correspondence 1964-67 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Meeting Minutes, 1983-90 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Members: Deceased, 1941-46 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Members: Deceased, 1960-69 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Members: Deceased, 1970-71 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Members: Deceased, 1972-73 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Members: Deceased, 1974-75 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Members: Deceased, 1976-77 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Members: Deceased, 1978-79 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Members: Deceased, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Members: Deceased, 1981-82 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Members: Deceased, 1983-84 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Members: Deceased, 1985-86 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Members: Deceased, 1987-88 (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - Members: Deceased, 1989-90 (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - Members: Dropped, Reinstated, Resigned, 1959-62, 1964, 1966-70 (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - Members: Dropped, Reinstated, Resigned - Howard Beard Affair, 1961 (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - Members: Dropped, Reinstated, Resigned, 1971-73 (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - Members: Dropped, Reinstated, Resigned, 1974-76 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Members: Dropped, Reinstated, Resigned, 1977-80 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Members: Dropped, Reinstated, Resigned, 1981-82 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Members: Dropped, Reinstated, Resigned, 1983-85 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Members: Dropped, Reinstated, Resigned, 1986-87 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Members: Dropped, Reinstated, Resigned, 1988-89 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Members: Dropped, Reinstated, Resigned, 1988-90 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Members: Emeritus, 1941-46 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Members: Emeritus, 1960-63 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Members: Emeritus, 1964-65 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Members: Emeritus, 1966-67 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Members: Emeritus, 1968-69 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Members: Emeritus, 1970 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Members: Emeritus, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Members: Emeritus, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Members: Emeritus, 1973 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Members: Emeritus, 1974 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Members: Emeritus, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Members: Emeritus, 1976, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Members: Honorary, 1959-62 (Box 32, Folder 20)